A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Abe Fellowships, Record Group 3, Series 8 FA1871
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship applicant declinations and withdrawals files, 1983-1994; 2; 6.175 Cubic Feet 16.25 document boxes: 16.25 letter boxes
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Stroup, Dorothy A. (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Sugiura, Tadashi (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Suttmeier, Richard P. (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Suzuki, Mitsuo (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Swann, Barbara B. (Box 10, Folder 159)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Tada, Eiko (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Tagashira, Shoichi (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Takanaka, Kimio (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Takasugi, Tadaaki (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Taniguchi, Tomohiko (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Tanno, Dai (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Thompson, Lee A. (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Tobin, John T. (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Tomii, Yukio (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Unoura, Hiroshi (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Uyeki, Eugene (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Van Ness, Peter (Box 11, Folder 171)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Vogel, Steven K. (Box 11, Folder 172)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Walker, Richard (Box 11, Folder 173)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Watanabe, Shinji (Box 11, Folder 174)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Wilsford, David (Box 11, Folder 175)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yamada, Teisuke (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yamada, Tetsuji (Box 11, Folder 177)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yamaguchi, Kaoru (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yamanaka, Keiko (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 withdrawals - Yamashige, Shinji, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yamauchi, Tomosaburo (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations - Yasuda, Yuki (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Zane, Kathleen (Box 11, Folder 183)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Yee, Albert (Box 11, Folder 184)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 declinations – Yu, Chia-yun (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Amako, Satoshi (Box 12, Folder 186)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Caron, David D. (Box 12, Folder 187)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Freeman, Laurie Anne (Box 12, Folder 188)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Fujimura, Joan H. (Box 12, Folder 189)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Horvat, Andrew, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 190)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Iida, Keisuke (Box 12, Folder 191)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kishima, Takako (Box 12, Folder 192)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Agawa, Naoyuki (Box 12, Folder 193)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Al-Marayati, Abid (Box 12, Folder 194)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Anegawa, Tomofumi (Box 12, Folder 195)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Bakos, Gabor (Box 12, Folder 196)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Beer, Jennifer (Box 12, Folder 197)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Blake, Sheri (Box 12, Folder 198)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Brahm, Richard (Box 12, Folder 199)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Brannon, Donald (Box 12, Folder 200)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Cummings, William K. (Box 12, Folder 201)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - D' Costa, Anthony (Box 12, Folder 202)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Dillon, Sara Ann (Box 12, Folder 203)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Dodge, Hiroko (Box 12, Folder 204)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Doi, Hiromoto (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Drotar, Mary Catherine (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Dunbar, Edward (Box 13, Folder 207)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Frank, Dana (Box 13, Folder 208)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Griswold, Jerome (Box 13, Folder 209)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Hollingsworth, Rogers J. (Box 13, Folder 210)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Ihonvbere, Julius (Box 13, Folder 211)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Ishiyama, Fumihiko (Box 13, Folder 212)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Friman, H. Richard (Box 13, Folder 213)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Galor, Oded (Box 13, Folder 214)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Givens, Stephen (Box 13, Folder 215)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Golub, Stephen (Box 13, Folder 216)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Goodman, Allen (Box 13, Folder 217)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Gorkin, Michael, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 218)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Johnstone, Bob, 1990-1993 (Box 13, Folder 219)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Jones, Kimberly A. (Box 13, Folder 220)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kawano, Hitoshi (Box 13, Folder 221)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kemper, Steven (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kenney, Martin (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kilner, John F. (Box 13, Folder 224)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kitayama, Shinobu (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kawabata, Yasuyuki (Box 13, Folder 226)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kitayama, Toshiya (Box 13, Folder 227)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kobayashi, Kohei (Box 13, Folder 228)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kono, Tsutomu, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 229)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kubota, Yuri (Box 14, Folder 230)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kuriki, Chieko, 1988-1993 (Box 14, Folder 231)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Kuroda, Yasumasa (Box 14, Folder 232)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Lewin, Arnie (Box 14, Folder 233)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - March, Robert M. (Box 14, Folder 234)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Masiero, Gilmar, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 235)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Matsuura, Itsuko (Box 14, Folder 236)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - McGill, Peter (Box 14, Folder 237)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Oda, Sobei H. (Box 14, Folder 238)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Methe, David (Box 14, Folder 239)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Molony, Kathleen (Box 14, Folder 240)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Mutoh, Nancy (Box 14, Folder 241)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Mutoh, Nobumichi (Box 14, Folder 242)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Nakagawa, Tadashi (Box 14, Folder 243)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Nonaka, Keiko (Box 14, Folder 244)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Oda, Makoto (Box 14, Folder 245)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Schaller, Michael (Box 14, Folder 246)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Schoenberger, Karl L. (Box 14, Folder 247)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Shoji, Yoshinobu (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Siegel, Jay (Box 14, Folder 249)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Sneider, Daniel (Box 14, Folder 250)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Soga, Kenichi (Box 14, Folder 251)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Spence, Nicola Adair (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Takasugi, Tadaaki (Box 14, Folder 253)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Tamura, Hideo (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Teruhisa, Kose (Box 14, Folder 255)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Tilton, Mark (Box 15, Folder 256)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Tsuneki, Atsushi (Box 15, Folder 257)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Walker, John (Box 15, Folder 258)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Wilhite, Hal (Box 15, Folder 259)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Wallons, Roberta (Box 15, Folder 260)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Yakubovsky, Vladimir (Box 15, Folder 261)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1993-1994 declinations - Zunes, Stephen (Box 15, Folder 262)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Alvito, Massimo (Box 15, Folder 263)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Aoki, Koji (Box 15, Folder 264)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Bob, Daniel (Box 15, Folder 265)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Brannigan, Michael C. (Box 15, Folder 266)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Caron, David, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 267)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Christensen, Raymond V. (Box 15, Folder 268)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Cohen, Stephen D. (Box 15, Folder 269)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Ellis, Roger (Box 15, Folder 270)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Farrell, William R. (Box 15, Folder 271)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Foley, Terence B. (Box 15, Folder 272)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Forsberg, Aaron (Box 16, Folder 273)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Fuhrman, Janice (Box 16, Folder 274)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Fujiwara, Kiichi (Box 16, Folder 275)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Funabashi, Reiko K. (Box 16, Folder 276)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Gao, Bai (Box 16, Folder 277)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Gorkin, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 278)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Gottfried, Heidi (Box 16, Folder 279)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Green, Michael Jonathan (Box 16, Folder 280)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Halloran, Richard (Box 16, Folder 281)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hasebe, Tadashi (Box 16, Folder 282)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hasegawa, Tsuyoshi (Box 16, Folder 283)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hein, Laura E. (Box 16, Folder 284)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Helgert, Joseph Peter (Box 16, Folder 285)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hirakawa, Takaaki (Box 16, Folder 286)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hojo, Hiroo (Box 16, Folder 287)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Hoover, William D. (Box 16, Folder 288)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Ihonvbere, Julius O. (Box 16, Folder 289)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Johnstone, Robert A. B. (Box 17, Folder 290)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Kiger, Joseph C. (Box 17, Folder 291)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Kinney, Carol J. (Box 17, Folder 292)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Kleeman, Faye Yuan (Box 17, Folder 293)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Kowalewski, David (Box 17, Folder 294)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Liao, Tim Futing (Box 17, Folder 295)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Lie, John J. (Box 17, Folder 296)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Linger, Daniel (Box 17, Folder 297)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Manifold, Diane L. (Box 17, Folder 298)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Mansor, Norma (Box 17, Folder 299)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Marsh, Terry A. (Box 17, Folder 300)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Mashima, Rieko (Box 17, Folder 301)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Matsumoto, Mari (Box 17, Folder 302)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Mendez, Deirdre (Box 17, Folder 303)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Methe, David T., 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 304)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Miller, Elizabeth (Box 17, Folder 305)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Mochizuki, Hiroshi (Box 17, Folder 306)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Morito, Hideyuki (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Neilan, Edward (Box 17, Folder 308)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Owada, Eiko (Box 17, Folder 309)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Ramachandran, Vijaya (Box 17, Folder 310)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Robbins, Donald James (Box 17, Folder 311)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Ryang, Sonia (Box 17, Folder 312)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Sato, Izumi (Box 18, Folder 313)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Siegel, Jay S. (Box 18, Folder 314)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Spence, Nicola Adair (Box 18, Folder 315)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Suranovic, Steven M. (Box 18, Folder 316)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Takase, Koichi (Box 18, Folder 317)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Takasugi, Tadaaki (Box 18, Folder 318)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Tanaka, Tatsuo (Box 18, Folder 319)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Tanatsugu, Masakazu (Box 18, Folder 320)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Tateno, Kazuyuki (Box 18, Folder 321)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Tourk, Khairy A., 1983-1994 (Box 18, Folder 322)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Tsukeda, Naoko (Box 18, Folder 323)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - White, James D. (Box 18, Folder 324)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Xiang, Lanxin (Box 18, Folder 325)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Yakubovsky, Vladimir (Box 18, Folder 326)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Yamazaki, Kazutami (Box 18, Folder 327)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Yamada, David T. (Box 18, Folder 328)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1994-1995 declinations - Yang, Chun Hee (Box 18, Folder 329)
- Fellowship applicant review general files, 1989-1992; 3; .19 Cubic Feet .5 document box: .5 letter box
  This subseries contains files pertaining to the review of applications to the Social Science Research Council's Abe Fellowship Program that are not individual applicant files. These materials primarily originate from the 1991-1992 competition, the Program's first year awarding the fellowship.
  The files document a preliminary round of review the Program conducted on fellowship applicants. These files include coversheets that describe if the Program selected the applicant to advance through the review round.
  The subseries also includes miscellaneous applicant reference letters and application form templates.
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 preliminary review – Cover sheets (Box 19, Folder 330)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 – Miscellaneous applicant references (Box 19, Folder 331)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Award 1991-1992 preliminary review – Cover sheets, 1989-1991 (Box 19, Folder 332)
  - Abe Fellowship Program envelopes - Application checklist forms, undated (Box 19, Folder 333)
- Chronology files, 1991-1995; 4; .95 Cubic Feet 2.5 document boxes: 2.5 letter boxes
  This subseries holds the chronology files of the Social Science Research Council's (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program. Chronology files contain correspondence for specific periods of time. The chronology files are divided between incoming and outgoing correspondence. Incoming correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the sender's name, and outgoing correspondence is arranged alphabetically by the addressee's name.
  Correspondence in the files documents different administrative and program activities of the Abe Fellowship Program. The communications discuss Abe Fellowship Program Committee membership and meetings as well as SSRC staffing. There are also communications about applications to the Abe Fellowship Program, fellows' research projects, planning and preparation for Fellows' Conferences, and program reviews. Some files contain correspondence between the Abe Fellowship Program and the Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) which provides insights into the relationship between the two organizations.
  - Chronology file - 1991-1992 incoming correspondence (Box 19, Folder 334)
  - Chronology file - 1993 incoming correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 335)
  - Chronology file - 1994 incoming correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 336-337)
  - Chronology file - 1991-1992 outgoing correspondence (Box 20, Folder 338-341)
  - Chronology file - 1992-1993 outgoing correspondence, part 1 (Box 20, Folder 342)
  - Chronology file - 1992-1993 outgoing correspondence, part 2 (Box 21, Folder 343-344)
  - Chronology file - 1994 outgoing correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 21, Folder 345-348)
- Meeting files, 1989-1995; 5; 1.71 Cubic Feet 4.5 document boxes: 4.5 letter boxes
  This subseries contains files documenting the organization and activities of various Social Science Research Council (SSRC) Abe Fellowship Program meetings. These meetings are primarily Program Committee Meetings and Annual Abe Fellows' Conferences from between the start of the Program and the mid-1990s.
  The subseries includes files devoted to supplemental materials for meetings such as Abe Fellowship proposal abstracts that were reviewed at Committee Meetings and workshop readings used at Fellows' Conferences. There are also files that concern Program reviews and reflections.
  Common material formats found throughout the subseries include agendas, briefing books, drafts, articles, reports, memos, correspondence, meeting minutes, and notes.
  - 1994 Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference workshop readings - Aging, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 349)
  - First Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1993, Tokyo, Japan (Box 22, Folder 350)
  - Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1994, Montauk, New York - Transcript (Box 22, Folder 351)
  - First Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1993, Tokyo, Japan - Draft agenda (Box 22, Folder 352-353)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1992-1993 proposal abstracts (Box 22, Folder 354)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1994-1995 proposal abstracts - Forwarded to Committee (Box 22, Folder 355)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1993-1994 proposal abstracts (Box 23, Folder 356)
  - Abe Fellowship Program 1992-1993 proposal abstracts (Box 23, Folder 357)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, October 1993 - Agenda (Box 23, Folder 358)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, July 1994 - Agenda (Box 23, Folder 359-360)
  - First Annual Abe Fellowship Program Fellows' Conference, July 1993, Tokyo, Japan - Briefing book (Box 23, Folder 361)
  - The Abe Fellowship Program: Year 1 (September 1991 – March 1992) - Report to Japan Foundation Center for Global Partnership (CGP) (Box 23, Folder 362-363)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, October 1994 - Agenda (Box 24, Folder 364-365)
  - Abe Fellowship Program Committee Meeting, July 1994 - Agenda (Box 24, Folder 366-367)